Muhammad Ilyasa

Phone Number: +62 895-1800-5870 | Email: muhammad.ilyaasa@gmail.com
GitHub: github.com/iyasz | Portfolio: iyasz.github.io/portfolio

Introduction

I am a Junior Website Developer and Fresh Graduate Software Engineering Student from Bina Mandiri Multimedia High School with experience as a Website Developer. I am a fast learner and self-taught. I have learned many new technologies in the past few years by myself from the internet.

Education and Awards

Bina Mandiri Multimedia High School

Software Engineering

2021 - 2024

- Award From School for Website Competition.
- Academic Award as a Student.

Experience

Solusi Data Pratama

Junior Quality Assurance Intern

Dec 2023 – Mar 2024

- Ensure proper application website validation, for readability.
- Testing the latest features developed, to make sure there are no bugs.

Freelance

Website Developer

Jan 2023 - Present

- Create a Laundry Website Application with online payment for Company.
- Develop a school profile website.

Featured Projects

- Komiktoon A website used to create comic content and read comic for free.
- **Go-Cashier** Program used to create Website-base Cashier Application.
- **Tokyo Finds** Simple merchandise store website application.

Skills

Programming Languages: PHP, Javascript, Golang, VB.Net. **Framework**: Bootstrap, Tailwind, JQuery, Fiber, Laravel, VueJS.

DBMS: MySQL, PostgreSQL. **Design**: Figma, Canva.

Languages: Indonesia (Native), English (Basic).

Interpersonal: Analytic Ability, Multi-tasking, Teamwork.

Certifications

- Web Development Telkom DigiUp (DigiUp Batch 1), 15 February 2023
- Quality Assurance Solusi Data Pratama (Intership Program), 14 March 2023